{
    "subject": "resource/Ainselu_Kharka",
    "predicate": "ontology/utcOffset",
    "object": "+5:45",
    "human_readable": "Ainselu Kharka is in UTC+5:45.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7837539911270142,
            "question": "What is the UTC time offset for Ainselu Kharka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597055435180664,
            "question": "Is Ainselu Kharka ahead of or behind Coordinated Universal Time (UTC)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7448568940162659,
            "question": "What time zone does Ainselu Kharka use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7401159405708313,
            "question": "What might be the local time in Ainselu Kharka at noon UTC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7308797836303711,
            "question": "How many hours is Ainselu Kharka ahead of UTC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7046175003051758,
            "question": "Are there any other places that use the same time zone as Ainselu Kharka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565538048744202,
            "question": "If it's 10:00 AM in UTC, what time is it in Ainselu Kharka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48559293150901794,
            "question": "Could you explain how UTC+5:45 works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4832480251789093,
            "question": "What factors might influence the choice of a specific time zone for a location like Ainselu Kharka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.031426046043634415,
            "question": "How does understanding time zones help with international communication and travel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ainselu Kharka is in UTC+5:45.",
            "html": "dbpedia_48_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might influence the choice of a specific time zone for a location like Ainselu Kharka?",
            "html": "dbpedia_48_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you explain how UTC+5:45 works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_48_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If it's 10:00 AM in UTC, what time is it in Ainselu Kharka?",
            "html": "dbpedia_48_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_48_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Ainselu Kharka, including that it is located in the Sagarmatha Zone of eastern Nepal and mentions its time zone as \"Nepal Time (UTC+5:45)\", which confirms the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Nepal Time (NST) was UTC+5:45 from 1986 to 2016, but since the introduction of DST in 2016, Nepal uses NST (UTC+5:45) only during winter, and NPT (UTC+5:30) during summer, which has a one-hour gap with the previous standard time.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}